Institute for First Amendment Studies Records MS074
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tax records, 1973 -- 1996; 1988 -- 1994; MS074.006; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - Foundation to Defend the First Amendment, 1993; MS074.006.018.00007 (Box 18)
  - Free Congress Foundation, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00008 (Box 18)
  - Free Market Foundation, 1989 -- 1995; MS074.006.018.00009 (Box 18)
  - Fundamentalists Anonymous, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.006.018.00010 (Box 18)
  - Future of Freedom Foundation, Inc., 1991 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00011 (Box 18)
  - Hall Foundation, 1989 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00012 (Box 18)
  - Helms Foundation, Inc., 1994; MS074.006.018.00013 (Box 18)
  - Human Life Foundation, 1975 -- 1995; MS074.006.018.00014 (Box 18)
  - Hume, Jaquelin Foundation, MS074.006.018.00015 (Box 18)
  - Hunt Oil Co., 1994; MS074.006.018.00016 (Box 18)
  - Huston Foundation, 1990 -- 1995; MS074.006.018.00017 (Box 18)
  - Individual Rights Foundation, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00018 (Box 18)
  - Institute for Creation Research 990s, 1989 -- 1995; MS074.006.018.00019 (Box 18)
  - International Broadcasting Network, 990 forms, 1992; MS074.006.018.00020 (Box 18)
  - Klingensmith, Agnes Charitable Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.018.00021 (Box 18)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.018.00022 (Box 18)
  - Lamb, Kirkland S. & Rena B. Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.018.00023 (Box 18)
  - Life Legal Defense Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.018.00024 (Box 18)
  - Lowell Berry Foundation, 1993; MS074.006.018.00025 (Box 18)
  - Henry Luce Foundation, 1 of 2, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00026 (Box 18)
  - Luce, Henry Foundation, 2 of 2, 1989 -- 1992; MS074.006.018.00027 (Box 18)
  - Mostyn Foundation, Inc., 1990 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00029 (Box 18)
  - Mountain States Legal Foundation, 1990 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00030 (Box 18)
  - NACE 990 Forms, National Association of Christian Educators, 1989 -- 1993; MS074.006.018.00031 (Box 18)
  - National Christian Charitable Foundation, Inc., 1994 -- 1995; MS074.006.018.00032 (Box 18)
  - National Commission of Catholic Laymen, 1978 -- 1995; MS074.006.018.00033 (Box 18)
  - National Forum Foundation, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00034 (Box 18)
  - National Legal Foundation 990s, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.006.018.00035 (Box 18)
  - The NRA Foundation Inc., 1993 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00036 (Box 18)
  - New York Family Research, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.006.018.00037 (Box 18)
  - New York Right to Life, 1989 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00038 (Box 18)
  - Oldham Little Church Foundation, 1990 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00039 (Box 18)
  - Olin, John M. Foundation, Inc. [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1995; MS074.006.018.00040 (Box 18)
  - Olin, John M. Foundation, Inc. [2 of 2], 1988 -- 1990; MS074.006.018.00041 (Box 18)
  - Oregon Citizens' Alliance, 1989 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00042 (Box 18)
  - Perkins, John M. Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.018.00043 (Box 18)
  - Phillips Foundation, Inc., 1992 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00044 (Box 18)
  - Plymouth Rock Foundation, 1989 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00045 (Box 18)
  - Points of Light Foundation, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00046 (Box 18)
  - Presbyterian Church in America Foundation, Inc., 1993 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00047 (Box 18)
  - Rainbow Fund, 1992 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00048 (Box 18)
  - Reason Foundation, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00049 (Box 18)
  - Regent College Foundation, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00050 (Box 18)
  - Right Wing Literary Research Associates, 990 Forms, 1993; MS074.006.018.00051 (Box 18)
  - Rutherford Institute, form 990, 1991 -- 1994; MS074.006.018.00052 (Box 18)
  - Scaife, Sarah Foundation, 1991 -- 1995; MS074.006.019.00001 (Box 19)
  - Scriptures for America, 990 forms, 1993; MS074.006.019.00002 (Box 19)
  - Selous Foundation, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.006.019.00003 (Box 19)
  - Simmons-Balser Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.019.00004 (Box 19)
  - Smith Richardson Foundation, 1993; MS074.006.019.00005 (Box 19)
  - Stewardship Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.019.00006 (Box 19)
  - Strategic Christian Services, 990 forms, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.006.019.00007 (Box 19)
  - Tamarak Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.019.00008 (Box 19)
  - Teaching Economics Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.019.00009 (Box 19)
  - The Tell Foundation, 1988 -- 1994; MS074.006.019.00010 (Box 19)
  - Tell, Paul P. Foundation, 1994; MS074.006.019.00011 (Box 19)
  - Texas Christian Coalition, 990 forms, 1992; MS074.006.019.00012 (Box 19)
  - Texas Public Policy Foundation, 1989 -- 1994; MS074.006.019.00013 (Box 19)
  - Traditional Value Coalition, 990 forms, 1993; MS074.006.019.00014 (Box 19)
  - Ware Foundation, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.006.019.00015 (Box 19)
  - Weir Foundation, 1989 -- 1994; MS074.006.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - World Medical Health Foundation, Inc., 1985 -- 1994; MS074.006.019.00017 (Box 19)
  - Young America's Foundation, 1991 -- 1994; MS074.006.019.00018 (Box 19)
  - 990 Forms, IRS, 1992 -- 1993; MS074.006.019.00019 (Box 19)
  - Notes, 1991; MS074.006.019.00020 (Box 19)
  - 990's - IFAS - respond to IRS, 1991 -- 1995; MS074.006.019.00021 (Box 19)
  - 990's awaiting IRS action, 1993 -- 1995; MS074.006.019.00022 (Box 19)
  - 990 requests and lists, 1993 -- 1994; MS074.006.019.00023 (Box 19)
  - Apparent dead ends, 1994; MS074.006.019.00024 (Box 19)
  - To be researched, 1992 -- 1995; MS074.006.019.00025 (Box 19)